{
    "id": "b7ec34344e7c45a4a0dc38a063e5175e",
    "title": "Subject - Verb Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Here are two pieces of shirting. Each one ………….. two meters long.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That woman ……………… got two children. Both ……………….. girls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have, is",
                "have, are",
                "has, are",
                "has, is"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Few girls in this village …………………. to schools.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Some economists believe that all …………….. not well with the global economy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He inherited a lot of wealth from his father, but now all ………………. gone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. all of the invitees expected to turn up?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have two pens. But neither ………………… well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writes"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "“Which of these two flats would you like to buy? “ “Either …………….. me.”",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "suit",
                "suits"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Mathews is an advocate, but neither of his two sons …………….. good at studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The two countries have been at war for three years now. Neither …………….. to agree to a ceasefire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}